Hello.
こんにちは
You're cute, aren't you?
可愛いね、あなたは
No, that's not true.
いや、そんなことないです
What's your name?
名前は?
This is Emi.
エミです
Emi-chan?
エミちゃん?
yes.
はい
Emi-chan, what kind of work do you do?
エミちゃん、何の仕事してるの?
I'm working as an office lady.
OLやってます
OL?
Are you busy with work?
仕事忙しい?
I'm busy.
忙しいです
That's right.
そうなんだ
What do you do on your day off?
休みの日は何やってるの?
I sleep on my days off.
休みの日は寝てる
I'm sleeping.
寝てるんだ
Is sleeping happy?
寝るのは幸せ?
yes.
はい
Is eating happy?
食べるのも幸せ?
I like it.
好きです
What do you like?
何好きなの?
What is it?
なんだろう?
ramen.
ラーメン
I like ramen.
ラーメンが好きなんだ
I like noodles.
麺類好きです
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
It's not pasta, it's ramen.
パスタとかじゃなくてラーメンなんだ
I like pasta.
パスタは好き
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
I like everything.
何でも好きだね
Yeah.
うん
There's nothing I don't like about it.
嫌いのもないじゃん
I like meat.
お 肉 は好き
Do you also like meat?
お肉も好き?
There's nothing I don't like about it.
嫌いのもないでしょ
That's a naughty body.
エッチな体だね
Mishan, you look pretty.
ミ シ ャン、おしろっきいね
It might be oshirokki.
おしろっきいかも
Oshirokii is erotic, isn't it?
おしろっきいのエロいよね
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
By yourself.
自分で
No, not that much.
いや、そんなに
What do you like about your body?
自分の体の中で好きなのどこ?
I don't know.
わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんない?
It's a face, a face.
顔だろ、顔
face?
顔?
cute.
可愛い
You like her face, right?
顔好きだろ
face.
顔
I like it.
好きだね
I always look in the mirror.
鏡の前見ちゃうね、いつもね
No, that's not true.
いやいや、そんなことないですよ
Is that so?
そう なの?
yes.
はい
When was the last time you had sex?
最近はいつエッチしたの?
Recently, about two weeks ago.
最近、2週間くらい前とか
I did it two weeks ago.
2週間前やったんだ
how was it?
どうだった?
it was good.
良かった
It's so funny.
すげえ笑うじゃん
You looked really good.
本当に良かった顔してんじゃん
it was good.
良かった
Did I say it?
言っちゃった?
What kind of person was he?
どういう人だったの?
Handsome.
イケメン
Handsome?
イケメン?
I like handsome guys.
イケメンが好きなんだ
I love handsome men.
イケメン大好き
Who do you like among handsome adults?
イケメン大人だったら誰が好きなの?
Hey.
へぇー
Kind of like Tanaka.
なんか田中系みたいな
I like kind people.
優しい感じの人が好きなんだね
It sure looks cool.
確かにかっこいいね
Black hair, like a sudden.
黒髪、突発みたいな
If you look closely, you'll see a naughty face.
よく見るとエッチな顔してるね
TRUE?
本当?
You like dick, right?
チンチン好きでしょ?
I really like it.
めっちゃ好き
on second thoughts?
やっぱり?
Yeah.
うん
How many people have experience?
経験人数何人くらい?
Hey.
へ ぇー
I haven't counted exactly, but I think there were about 10 people.
ちゃんと数えてないけど、 10人くらいかな
About 10 people?
10人くらい?
Are they all good-looking?
全員イケメン?
Handsome.
イケメン
They're all good-looking guys.
全員イケメンなんだ
That's amazing.
すごいな
Is there a one night love?
ワンナイトラブもあるの?
When I was a student.
学生の頃
I see, are you going to a club or something?
そっか、クラブとか行ってってこと?
Yeah, people around there.
うん、その辺にいる人
People around there.
その辺にいる人
What about Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃんどう?
What about Emi?
えみちゃんは?
cute?
可愛い?
cute.
可愛い
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いよね
Even the words are white.
言葉も白いし
You're clinking right now and it's cute.
今クリクリしてて可愛いね
TRUE?
本当?
I wish I could have done it as an idol.
アイドルでもやればよかったじゃん
why?
なんで?
I can't.
できないよ
You can do it.
できるよ
I should have applied.
応募すればよかったじゃん
It might have been on TV right now.
今テレビ出てたかもね
It's not out.
出てないよ
I'm about to be filmed a naughty video.
今からエッチな動画撮られちゃうけど
fun.
楽しみ
fun?
楽しみ?
yes.
はい
Aren't you nervous?
緊張しないの?
I'm nervous, but I'm also looking forward to it.
緊張するけど、楽しみが余ってる
superior?
上?
I see.
そっか
It's perverted, really.
変態だね、本当に
He really is a pervert.
本当に変態なんだな
Your skin is white too.
肌も白いね
It's white.
白いですね
Don't you walk outside?
外で歩かないの?
Not much.
あんまり
It's not outside.
外でないです
Indoors.
インドアで
In the house.
家の中で
what are you doing at home?
家の中で何してるの?
everytime.
いつも
Eh.
えー
I'm an indoor person.
室内派なんで
Indoor style?
室内派?
Are you watching Netlix?
ネットリックス見たりしてるのかな?
I watch Netflix and YouTube.
ネ ットリックス見たり、YouTube見たり
Have sex.
エッチしたり
Are you reading about yourself?
自分の辺読んじゃうの?
Where do I read it?
どこで読むの?
vice versa.
逆に
That man isn't going home.
その男のさ、お家に行かないんだ
I go when I have to, but it's easier for me.
行くときは行くけど、自分の方が楽だから
I'll read it.
読んじゃうんだ
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'm delivering.
デリバリーしてる
Like a business trip.
出張みたいな
I see.
そうか
You have a strong sexual desire.
性欲強いね
Annoying.
うざいっつ的な
I see.
なるほどね
One dick.
ちんこいっつ
He's young and perverted, really.
若いのに変態だね、本当に
I see.
そっか
Well then, can you take it off for a second?
じゃあさ、ちょっとさ、それ脱がしてもいい?
Are you going to take it off?
脱ぐの?
Because I want to see your body.
体見たいからさ
Kuro-chan, look.
黒ちゃん、ほら
Do you have it?
持ってる?
Look this way.
こっち向いて
You can have it.
持てるよね
I can't have it.
持てない
You definitely have it.
絶対持ててるでしょ
I think I definitely have it.
絶対持ててると思うんだけど
I can't have it.
持てないよ
Don't lie.
嘘つくな
I really can't have it.
本当に持てない
show me.
見せて
Emi-chan, your breasts are big.
えみちゃん、おっぱい大きいね
soft.
柔らかい
This is soft, Kuro-chan.
柔らかい、黒ちゃん、これ
It's insanely soft.
めちゃめちゃ柔らかい
Wow, this.
うわ、これ
You have an erotic body.
エロい体してるね
That's good.
それがいいわ
You like having boobs too, right?
おっぱいもあるの好きでしょ
What do you think?
どうで?
Kuro-chan, move a little.
ちょっと黒ちゃん動いて
Try standing up!
立ってみてみよっ
mosquito.
か
Wow.
うわ ー
Your butt is big.
お尻大きいね
Really.
本当に
How many cup breasts is this?
おっぱい何カップこれ?
There's something like a D cup.
Dカップとかがあるよ
D cup?
Dカップ?
There's more, right?
もっとあるでしょ
Oh, I don't know.
え、わかんない
Well, I have a lot to eat today, so I have to give you a cup and go home.
じゃあ今日、いっぱいもんでさ、1カップあげて帰んなきゃね
I will do that.
そうします
Will you do that?
そうする?
I see.
そ っか
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみて
Wow, I was able to wear a thong.
うわ、Tバックできたんだ
Wow, this is a spectacular view.
うわ、これ絶景だよ、これ
Amazing view.
すごい絶景
Do you get sexually harassed at work?
会社でさ、セクハラされるでしょ
Eh, it won't happen.
え、されないよ
It won't happen.
されないよ
There are no men at work.
男の人いないよ、職場に
Well, as I said, I'm the receptionist, so I don't really get involved.
え、言うけど、受付だから私は、 だからあんまり関わらない
Who are the people at the company?
会社の人とは
Aren't you going to do something?
なんぱされないの?
sometimes.
たまに
Does it happen sometimes?
たまにされる?
Are there many uncles?
おじさんが多いの?
Nanpaha.
なんぱは
Hmm, I'm not that type of person.
う ーん、あんまタイプじゃない
It's not my type.
タイプじゃないんだ
I see.
そっか
I got it a while ago.
ちょっと前に手ついてこら
Wow.
うわ
This is a perverted ass.
お尻変態だよ、これ
Only good-looking guys have ever entered.
イケメンしか入ったことない
hole.
穴
Right?
でしょ?
Kuro-chan, which butt?
黒ちゃん、どのお尻?
Wow, pink.
すごい、ピンク色
Pink?
ピンク色?
Kuro-chan, have you seen her pussy yet?
黒ちゃん、もうマンコ見ちゃってんの?
Oh, Kiwa, Kiwa.
あ、キワね、キワね
Here.
ここね
Wow, this is just the last minute.
うわ、ギリギリだね、これね
What type do you like?
ど んなタイプが好きなの?
I like A-Pac and Hijoito.
エーパックか、ひじょういとか好き
I like things that are terrible.
ひじょういとか好きなんだ
Yeah.
うん
Try doing some MG on this.
これちょっとMGしてみて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
which one?
どれ?
It's delicious.
うまいよ
Can you see me?
おケケ見えてる?
this.
これ
Okeke.
おケケ
Have you never had a shaved pussy?
パイパンにしたことないの?
Well, there is.
えー、あるよ
Wouldn't it be better to have a gift?
おケケあったほうが?
like?
好き?
now.
今は
Yeah, I like it.
うん、好き
I see.
そっか
Aren't you going to get wet?
濡れちゃうんじゃない?
If I was touching it.
触ってたら
Kuro-chan, why don't you tighten it up a little?
黒ちゃん、ちょっといっぱい締めよっか、
today.
今日
It's about Meme-chan.
めめちゃんのことね
You must be happy, teasing me so cutely.
幸せでしょ、こんな可愛くいじめて
I want to tease you quickly.
早くいじめたい
I think I'll take a look at this.
見ちゃおうかな、これ
good?
いい?
this.
これ
Beautiful, boobs.
きれいだね、おっぱい
real?
ほんと?
Those are beautiful breasts.
きれいなおっぱいだね
happy.
うれしい
Does your tingling feel good?
チクビ気持ちいいの?
Yeah, it feels good.
うん、気持ちいい
Do you prefer pussy or dick?
おまんこと、チクビどっち好き?
Well, I really like it.
えー、本当に好き
The look on your face is cute.
感じてる顔、可愛いね
Kuro-chan, take off your bra!
クロちゃん、ブラサー外しよっ
mosquito.
か
That's naughty.
エ ッチだね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
This was taken.
これ、撮られて
No, it's embarrassing.
いや、恥ずかしいよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
But isn't it fun?
でも楽しいでしょ?
He's a pervert.
変態だもんな
I like this butt.
このお尻が好きだな
Have you ever been laid off?
仲出しされたことあるの?
everytime.
いつも
Do you always have sex?
いつも仲出しなの?
He's really perverted.
ほ んと変態だな
Kuro-chan, let's lick this a little.
クロちゃん、これちょっと舐めてみよっか
Look down.
下見てみ
copper?
どう?
You got licked.
舐められちゃったね
There are a lot of chikubi standing here.
こっちのチクビいっぱい立ってるよ
Kuro-chan, what do you think?
クロちゃん、どう?
taste.
味
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
Looks delicious.
おいしそうやわ
It smells like a girl.
女 の子の匂いがするね
Does it smell good?
いい匂いする?
I'll buy some pussy scent later.
後でさ、マンコの匂いも買おうよ
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいでしょ?
It smells like pussy.
マンコの匂いな
It's become hard.
固くなっちゃってんじゃん
I'm pulling you, you know.
引っ張っちゃってるよ、ほら
How do your breasts feel?
おっぱいの気持ち?
I'll lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めるからね
Kuro-chan, aren't you already getting an erection?
クロちゃん、もう勃起しちゃってんじゃないの?
A little from the beginning.
最初からちょっと
nice.
いいね
Kuro-chan, try licking this too.
クロちゃん、こっちも舐めてみよ
That's nice.
いいなぁ
It feels good, little one.
気持ちいいんだ、チクビ
Take Icchi's side jaw.
いっちな横顎を取る
Your voice has come out.
声出てきたね
Are you feeling better?
気持ちよくなってきた?
Are you excited to be taken?
取られて興奮してんでしょ?
Hey.
ねえ
Kuro-chan, is it delicious?
クロちゃん、美味しい?
It's delicious.
美味しいよな
This looks delicious.
美味しそうだな、これ
If this happens.
こうなったら
So, let's go to bed and let me see your pussy.
じゃあ、ベッドさ、行ってさ、 おマンコ見せてもらおうか
Kuro-chan, get me a bed.
クロちゃん、ベッド取ってあげて
Spread your legs.
足広げて
I think I can see it for a while.
ちょっとはみれそうだよ
Isn't it a bit dangerous?
ちょっと危ないんじゃない?
a little bit.
ちょっと
I could see the side of her pussy just now.
ちょっと今、おマンコの横も見えたよ
Hey, that's strange.
ねえ、おかしい
Now, turn around and take your pants off, okay?
じゃあさ、後ろ向きになってさ、 パンツ下ろしちゃっていい?
Okay, let's try it.
よし、やってみようか
Kuro-chan, where is your butt?
クロちゃん、どこのお尻?
That's an impressive ass.
この迫力満点のお尻だよ
beautiful.
綺麗
Look at your butthole too.
お尻の穴もほら、 ね
This is a nice view.
これ、いい景色だね
Emi-chan, look this way.
エミちゃん、こっち向いてみ
Would you like me to show you your face?
お顔見せてもらおうか
yes.
そう
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
You're doing a naughty pose.
イッチなポーズしてるね
hey.
ね
Kuro-chan, let's smell your butt.
クロちゃん、お尻の匂い嗅いでみ
copper?
どう?
The smell of a girl.
女の子の匂い
The one with the hole smells like a girl.
穴あるもん、女の子の匂いするんだ
Emi-chan is amazing.
エミちゃん、すごいね
There's no smell.
臭いとこないんだね
Emi-chan.
エミちゃんね
Everything smells good.
全部いい匂いじゃん
Kuro-chan, look.
クロちゃん、ほら
Take a picture, take it slow.
撮ってみ、ゆっくり
Isn't it wet?
濡れてるんじゃない?
That's a beautiful pussy.
綺麗なマンコだね
In pink.
ピンクで
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's a little wet.
ちょっと濡れてるよ
Look.
ほら
It's shiny.
テカテカしてるじゃん
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
恥ずかしいでしょ
hey.
ね
I'm dropping it.
落としてるよ
Pichu picchu is ringing.
ピチュピチュ鳴ってるよ
Please sit facing the front.
正面向いて座ってこい
I'll take lots of close-up shots.
いっぱいアップで撮るから
Even if you open it.
開いても
Have them open it themselves.
自分で思いっきり開いてもらう
Pichu picchu sounded.
ピチュピチュ鳴ったね
good?
いい?
I'll take a picture.
撮るよ
It's wet, isn't it?
濡れてるでしょ
Isn't your clit standing up a little too?
クリもちょっと立ってるんじゃない?
this.
これ
It's true, I'm taking pictures.
ほ んとだ、撮ってる
Feeling amazing?
すごい気持ち?
Chestnut.
クリ
Open it wide.
いっぱい開いて
You look amazing, Emi-chan.
めっちゃな顔してるね、エミちゃんね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
feeling
気持ち
good?
いい?
It's warm.
温 かいね
I'm in.
入っちゃったよ
Does your pussy feel good?
おまんこ気持ちいい?
You can see everything.
全部見られちゃうね
I think I can see it once.
1回まで見えそう
Look, Kuro-chan.
見てごらん、クロちゃん
I'll inhale it.
吸い込んじゃう
Take a little Krittel bath.
ちょっとクリッテル風呂してみ
How does it smell?
匂いはどう?
The smell.
匂いは
What does Kuro-chan smell like?
クロちゃんどんな匂いする?
The smell of a girl.
女の子の匂い
It smells like a girl again.
また女の子の匂い
I'll take a picture of your naughty face.
エッチな顔撮っちゃうよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
What are you doing now?
今何されてるの?
Cree is being licked.
クリー舐められてる
My pussy was licked.
おまんこ舐められちゃったんだ
You're doing naughty things.
エッチなことしてるね
cute face
かわいい顔
Kuro-chan, your pussy is a mess.
クロちゃんぐちゃぐちゃでしょ、おまんこ
Muddy.
ドロドロ
It's muddy, isn't it?
ドロドロだよね
I want to lick Kuro-chan every day.
クロちゃん毎日舐めたいね
It's delicious.
うまいね
It's a little long though.
ちょっと長いけどね
It's embarrassing to be photographed in so many naughty places.
いっぱいやらしいところ撮られて恥ずかしいね
But it feels good, right?
でも気持ちいいでしょ?
It's already a match.
もう一致だ
Look at Kuro-chan's muddy pussy,
クロちゃんドロドロのまんこ見して、
Open it.
開いて
That's amazing, go all the way.
すごいね、奥までほら
It's all painted over.
全部塗れちゃって
It's pulling fast.
あ っと引いてる
It's blood, Emi-chan.
血だな、エミちゃん
It's kind of melty.
なんかトロトロだよね
It's stuck to your finger, see.
指に引っ付いてるよ、ほら
Black
ク ロ
Chan, can I guess the phone?
ちゃん、 電話当てちゃおうか
Shall I tease Emi-chan?
エミちゃんいじめちゃおうか
I like phone calls.
電話好き
Emi-chan, do you like phone calls?
エミちゃん電話好きなの?
I'll do a lot.
いっぱいやるよ
good?
いい?
Where does it feel good?
どこ気持ちいいの?
Does it feel good to swing?
振り気持ちいい?
You'll be standing up a lot.
いっぱい立っちゃうね
It's all visible.
全部映ってるよ
Emi
エミ
chan It's melty.
ちゃん トロトロだ
It feels good to shake the hole too, right?
穴も振るの気持ちいいでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Try shaking it.
振ってみてよ
I'll touch everything.
全部触っちゃうよ
No good
ダメ
is.
だ
it hurts.
痛 い
amazing.
すごい
Blow it up.
吹き吹きして
Emi-chan, open it.
エ ミちゃん開いてほら
Open the phone and look.
電話すっぽり開いてほら
Try opening it.
開いてみして
Emi-chan is gone.
エミちゃんいっちゃったね
I found this after all.
これ見つけやっぱり
I'm tingling.
ヒクヒクしてるもんね
Emi-chan, you'll do it yourself, right?
エミちゃんさ、自分でやるんでしょ?
At home.
うちで
Show it to a woman.
女に見せてよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I can show it to you.
見せれるよね
Please come earlier.
も っと前に来てもらう
Sit there on the edge of the bed.
そこのベッドの端に座って
Surprise me.
びっくりやってね
I'll take a naughty look.
イッチな顔撮るから
How do you do it?
どうやってやってんの?
everytime.
いつも
I'm sleeping.
寝てる
You look so naughty.
すごいイッチな顔してるよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'll shoot the manfish.
マンコウ撃つよ
Goodbye shoot.
さよなら撃て
Wow, that's a really naughty look on your face.
うわ、すごいイッチな顔撃ってんじゃん
Look, I'm getting wet from the inside.
ほら、中から濡れてきたよいっぱい
Hikuhiku-chan, this is amazing.
ヒクヒクちゃんすごいねこれ
I'm getting really wet.
すっげー濡れてきた
This is a perverted pussy.
変態のマンコウだこれ
Wow, you sleep really well.
いやーすごい寝るのね
I'm turning bright red, Manko.
真っ赤になってきたよマンコウ
Bright red.
真っ赤
I like it.
俺好きだね
Like this.
こうやって
Do you like being teased?
おじられるの好き?
Hey, come in.
ほら、入って
Wow, I'm being pushed out.
すごい、押し出されちゃう
That's it.
イ ッ チね
You like this more than anything, right?
この上好きでしょ?
Everything came in
全部入ってきた
Yo.
よ
I'm trembling inside.
中 でビクビクしてるよ
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Manko is warm.
マンコウあったかいね
Can I put a vibrator in it?
バイブ入れちゃっていい?
Vibrator.
バイブ
Can I try it?
入れてみていい?
Vibrator.
バイブ
Let's put Kuro-chan's vibrator in.
クロちゃんバイブ入れちゃおうよ
The one that moves.
ふいーんって動かすやつ
Would you like to sleep more?
もっと寝てごらん?
I swallowed it all.
全部飲み込んじゃった
Does your pussy feel good?
マ ンコウ気持ちいい?
Pussy feels good.
マンコウ気持ちいい
You're really wet.
すごい濡れちゃってるよね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Grigly.
グリグリ
Everything goes in.
全部入る
It's tough.
きついね
It's narrow, you see.
狭くて、ほら
This feels good pussy.
これ気持ちいいマンコウ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Look, it's kind of dripping.
なんか垂れてるじゃん、ほら
Like soup.
汁みたいな
There's water bubbles in it.
水ぼぼ入ってる
Are you thinking of going?
行っちゃいそうなの?
Go ahead.
行ってごらんよ
show me.
見せて
Ah, I'm gone.
あー、行っちゃった
I could see your face.
行った顔通れたね
I went there feeling good.
気持ちよくて行っちゃったね
That's amazing, Kuro-chan.
めっちゃだね、クロちゃん
Kuro-chan, would you like me to lick you?
クロちゃん、舐めてもらおうか
I agree.
そうだね
Nemi-chan is soaking in the afterglow.
ネミちゃん、余韻に浸ってる
You can't think when you're gone.
行っちゃって頭考えられないでしょ
Wow, that's amazing.
うわー、すごいね
Kuro-chan, let me show you the head of the earth.
クロちゃん、地首見せてもらおう
This cute face.
この可愛い顔
Nemi-chan, let me lick you.
ネミちゃん、舐めてもらおう
Jiku.
地首
Vero is so naughty.
ベロ、エッチだね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
What a beautiful face.
すごい顔きれい
Kuro-chan, what do you think?
クロちゃん、どう?
This is Ei-chan's tongue.
こっち、エイちゃんのベロ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's soft and feels good.
柔らかくて気持ちいい
So cute, Yumi-chan.
すげー可愛い、ユミちゃん
Do you always lick me like that?
そうやっていつも舐めてんの?
Handsome nipples.
イケメンの乳首
delicious?
美味しい?
I want to lick this.
こっちを舐めたい
The opposite too.
反対も
Yumi, you're cute.
ユミ、可愛いね
This is so cute.
すごい可愛いよ、これ
Do you always stand up and lick me when you're not that naughty?
いつもそんなエッチないと立てて舐めるの?
That's naughty.
エ ッチだな
Kuro-chan, didn't you stand up?
クロちゃん、立っちゃったんじゃない?
Let me take off your pants.
パンツ脱がしてもらおう
Can I take off my pants?
パンツ脱がしていいの?
Okay, take it easy.
いいよ、ゆっくりね
Kuro-chan, you're standing up.
クロちゃん、立っちゃってるね
It's really standing up.
めっちゃ立ってる
Well then, take a quick look.
じゃあさ、先っぽチロチロしてね
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
delicious.
美味しい
You're standing up amazingly, Kuro-chan.
すごい立ってるじゃん、クロちゃん
Kuro-chan, the tip feels good, right?
クロちゃん、先っぽ気持ちいいでしょ?
It feels so good.
めちゃめちゃ気持ちいい
Just look at it.
ふわえてごらんほら
Would you like to add another one?
もう一本くらいふわえてみ?
This is ticking, Kuro-chan.
カチカチだね、クロちゃん、これ
So cute.
かわいいな
I'll add this later.
これ後から入れるんだよ
fun.
楽しみ
Why don't you lick it slowly?
ゆっくり舐めてごらん?
It looks so delicious when you lick it.
すごい 美味しそうに舐めるね
black
クロ
Hold Emi-chan's head.
ちゃん、 エミちゃんの頭を持って
A little deeper.
ちょっと奥まで
It's really painful.
めっちゃ苦しいね
Your mouth is full of dick.
チンチンでいっぱいだね、お口ね
So bad.
すごい悪い
It's ticking.
カチカチね
Was it painful to go deep inside?
奥まで入って苦しかったの?
Come on, talk a lot.
ほら、いっぱい喋ってごらん
It's painful.
苦しいね
Kuro-chan, let's go to bed.
クロちゃん、じゃあベッド行こうか
Come here.
こっちおいで
Let me lie down and let you lick me.
横になって舐めてもらおう
What kind of penis do you like?
どんなチンチンが好きなの?
What kind of dick do you like?
どんなチンチンが好き?
It's hard and okay.
硬くてオッケーの
Is it like this?
こんなの?
Don't be naughty.
やらしくいかないでね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
So cute.
かわいろい
Kuro-chan feels good
クロちゃん、気持ちいい
hey.
ね
So cute, Mi-chan.
か わいいね、ミちゃん
Try eating everything from the bottom.
下から全部食べてみて
The head.
頭の方
Try licking it from the bottom to the tip.
下から先っぽまでペロってやってみ
That's right, Vetch.
そうそうそう、ベッチだね
It's so erotic.
すごいエロい
Wow.
うわー
Kuro-chan, you're getting eaten.
ク ロ ちゃん、食べられちゃってるね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Look, you've got your fingers crossed, Kuro-chan.
ほら、先パンパンじゃん、クロちゃん
That's amazing.
すごいよ
See, if you do that, you'll twitch.
ほら、それやったらピクピクしちゃうよ
Kuro-chan, don't you want to come in already?
クロちゃん、もう入れたいんじゃないの?
Yeah, and that.
うん、それと
Shall I add some sauce?
ソ ース入れちゃおうか
Chan-chan, straddle me.
ちゃんちゃん、上またがってこい
Chan-chan, let's go in.
ちゃんちゃん、入っちゃうね
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
Wow, that's cute.
わー、かわいいな
Let's put it in.
入 れ ちゃ う ね
Okay.
オッケー
Can you do it?
できるか
Yume-chan, let me come in.
ゆめちゃん、入れちゃおうか
Shirt holder?
シャツ入れ?
It's getting hot.
熱くなっちゃったんだ
Wow, this is silver.
うわー、銀銀これ
I'm going to put this in.
入れちゃうの、これ
Yume-chan, please put it in slowly.
ゆめちゃん、ゆっくり入れてみ
Here, I'll take a look.
ほ ら、見ててあげる
Wow.
うわー
Ah, I'm in.
あー、入っちゃった
I went in.
入 っちゃった
Kuro-chan, what happened?
クロちゃん、どうなった?
Is it warm?
あったかい?
Isn't it super slimy?
超ぬるぬるしてそうじゃない?
Wow, that's amazing.
うわー、すっごいな
Here, let me show you more.
ほら、もっと見せてみ
It went all the way in.
奥までズッポリ入っちゃったね
I went straight in.
ズッポリ入っちゃった
This is so naughty.
すっごいエッチだよ、これ
Wow, your face is erotic.
うわー、顔エロいな
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Wow, that's cute.
すごい、かわいいぞ
Don't you want to move more?
もっと動かしたいんじゃない?
I want to move more.
もっと動かしたい
Okay.
いいよ
Chin-chan, let me taste it.
いっぱいチンちゃん、味わってもらう
I'll take your naughty face.
エッチな顔、とってあげる
Yes, I'll take it.
うん、とってあげる
Wow.
うわー
Awesome.
すっごい
You're so intense, Yume-chan.
すっごい激しいね、ゆめちゃん
Look, I'm facing this way.
ほら、こっち向いた
oh yeah.
そうそう
You look nice.
気持ちいい顔してるよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You look so comfortable.
すっごい気持ちいい顔してる
Your butt is so big and erotic, isn't it?
すっごいお尻でっかくてエロいね、
this.
これ
Wow, it's all in there.
うわー、ズッポリ入ってる
Yume-chan feels so good.
ゆ め ちゃん、気持ちいいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You look like you're about to leave.
行っちゃいそうな顔してるじゃん、
already.
もう
I'm about to go.
行きそうになる
I feel like leaving.
行っちゃいそうになる
Kuro-chan, you're so happy, you have such a beautiful pussy.
黒ちゃん、幸せだね、こんな美人のおまんこ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Please move a lot.
い っぱい動いてもらって
This is erotic.
エ ロいな、これ
This face is naughty.
顔、エッチだな、これ
Kuro-chan, let's use this from behind.
黒ちゃん、これ、後ろからさ、いっぱいつこうよ
On Yume-chan's chest.
ゆ めちゃんの胸に
Yume-chan, turn around and lie on your side.
ゆめちゃん、後ろ向きにさ、横かかってさ
This way, face diagonally.
こっち、斜めにさ、向いてさ
vice versa.
逆に
Have them lean back.
後ろに横かかってもらう
Look, you can come in and see everything, this.
ほら、入って、全部見える、これ
Wow, that's naughty.
うわ、エッチだね、
this.
これ
It's Poli,
ぽ りだよ、
this.
これ
Kuro-chan, follow me from below.
黒 ちゃん、下からついて、これ
More and more, look.
もっともっと、ほら
Emi-chan is also covered more.
もっと、エミちゃんもつきまくって
It's soggy.
ぐちょぐちょいって
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
This feels good.
気持ちいいね、これ
Looks like it's going to go away.
いっちゃだそう
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
There's a white one out there.
白いの出てんじゃん
Okay, let's go to Emi-chan, this.
はい、エミちゃんに行きよう、これ
Well then, Kuro-chan, let's do it from behind.
じゃあ、黒ちゃん、後ろからやっちゃおうか
Show me that, ass.
それ、見せてね、お尻
Look at your butthole too.
お尻の穴も、ほら
Look, I'm naughty.
ほ ら、エッチだ、私
Look, there's a hole.
穴あるも、ほら
This is beautiful.
綺麗だね、これ
Shall we go?
行っちゃおうか
Can I put it in?
入れるの?
Let's put it in.
入れてみよう
Oh, nuru is so naughty.
おぉ、ぬるって、エッチだね
Emi-chan, your butt is huge and naughty.
エミちゃん、お尻でっかくて、エッチだね、
this.
これ
It feels so good.
なんか気持ちいい
That's right, I'm glad you're here.
そうそう、いられてんね、ほら
copper?
どう?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Yeah, it feels good.
うん、気持ちいい
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Did you get a lot?
いっぱいついてもらえた?
It feels good.
気持ちよさそう
It's all in there,
ズボズボ入ってるよ、
this.
これ
Look, there's some white naughty stuff out there.
ほ ら、白いエッチなの出てるよ、
It's white naughty.
白いエッチなの
Kuro-chan, this.
黒ちゃん、これ
Put your feet up, look.
足あげて、ほら
Yes, please show me a lot.
はい、ちょっと、いっぱい見せて
There's a lot in this.
ズボズボ入ってるよ、これ
amazing.
すごい
Look, this looks good.
ほら、よく見える、これ
beautiful.
綺麗
Ah, that's amazing.
あー、もうすごい
Kuro-chan, you did your best to follow me.
黒ちゃん、思いっきりついてもらえた
Let's go, that face.
いっちゃう、その顔
I'm going.
いっちゃう
I'll go.
いっちゃうね
Stick, stick, stick, stick,
くい、くい、くい、くい、
Kui.
く い
It's gone.
いっちゃったね
It's so beautiful, look.
すごい綺麗だよ、ほら
A face that says
いってる顔
Emi-chan is so beautiful.
エミちゃん、すごい綺麗
I couldn't put any effort into it anymore.
力入んなくなっちゃったね
amazing.
すごい
Well then, lay this down.
じゃあ、これ横にしてさ
Give me your legs.
足あげてさ
Show me your pussy, come on.
おまんこ見せて、ほら
Black-chan, open your pussy and look.
黒ちゃん、おまんこ開いて、ほら
Emi-chan, turn to me, look.
エミちゃん、こっち向いて、ほら
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's opening up more.
もっと開いてかかってる
This peeler is naughty.
ピーラーがエッチだね、これ
Kuro-chan, what do you think?
黒ちゃん、どう?
This is inside.
これ、中
It's crazy.
めっちゃしまう
I'll take a lot of your naughty insides.
エッチの中をいっぱい取ってあげる
It's so cute.
すごいかわいいよ
Look, I'm standing up.
ほら、ちくび立っちゃった
It was crispy, you see.
くりぴんぴんだったね、ほら
Kuro-chan, please move.
黒ちゃん、動いてもらおうか
Black-chan, in missionary position.
黒ちゃんさ、正常位でさ
Let's have a closer look.
もういっきりついてもらおう
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Look, there's a lot in there.
ほら、つぼづぼ入ってるよ
Chinchinkimochi.
ちんちんきもち
I love penises.
ちんちん大好きだもんね
Feeling.
きもち
I hope you have lots of them.
いっぱいついてもらいな
Please have lots and lots of them.
い っぱい、いっぱいついてもらい
Even the lips.
唇もいっそ
That's naughty.
エッチだな
It's so cute.
めっちゃベロかわいいね
Kuro-chan, you came out great.
黒ちゃん、すっごい出たね
Can you lick this?
これ、それなめてもらえん?
This is super cute.
めっちゃすごいかわいいよ、これ
A face licking a dick.
ち んちんなめてる顔
So cute.
すっごいかわいい
There were so many.
めっちゃいっぱいいっちゃったね
See the spirit.
精神ほら
It was said out loud.
口に出されちゃった
Take it out and see.
出してほら
It came out really dark.
すっごい濃いの出てきたね
It's very dark.
めっちゃ濃い
It was so cute.
すごいかわいかったよ
thank you.
ありがとう
how was it?
どうだった?
I want to have sex again.
またエッチしたい
Do you want to have sex again?
またエッチしたい?
Kuro-chan was great.
黒ちゃんよかったね
Let's go together again.
また一緒に行ってしようね
thank you.
ありがとう